<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>REALMLORDS</title>
      <link>https://realmlords.dev</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on REALMLORDS</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>Golden Bow</title>
    <link>https://realmlords.dev/System/Items/Weapons/Golden-Bow</link>
    <guid>https://realmlords.dev/System/Items/Weapons/Golden-Bow</guid>
    <description>Bows used by the legendary archers of the City of Gold are made to enhance their supreme skill. Each has gold worked through the grain of the wood, appearing like an elegant kintsugi.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 01:44:41 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Xanthicon</title>
    <link>https://realmlords.dev/System/Items/Poison/Xanthicon</link>
    <guid>https://realmlords.dev/System/Items/Poison/Xanthicon</guid>
    <description>A noxious agent brewed by the warriors of Xanthe, distilled from whole serpents, excrement, and deadly herbs reduced over a number of days in boiling cauldron.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 01:33:17 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Arkanythera Mechanism</title>
    <link>https://realmlords.dev/System/Magic-Items/Devices/Arkanythera-Mechanism</link>
    <guid>https://realmlords.dev/System/Magic-Items/Devices/Arkanythera-Mechanism</guid>
    <description>An Arkanythera Mechanism, known also as the “spell turner” is a finely crafted device designed to interrupt hostile spellcasting. Intricate clockwork is inscribed with runes representing the three moons, forces of Law and Chaos, as well as each of the base elements.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 01:11:01 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Opportunities at Aimilus</title>
    <link>https://realmlords.dev/Campaign/Opportunities-at-Aimilus</link>
    <guid>https://realmlords.dev/Campaign/Opportunities-at-Aimilus</guid>
    <description>Staying a season at Aimilus opportunities abound to make practical gains on the knowledge you have encountered. OpportunityTimeLearn Learn language moon book crafting book summoning book firedancing buisiness interest () research apprentice to Fontus ability score increase Spending Coin Firedancer Enclave Merchants of the Margaritifer Fontus’ Wares GoodCostExceptional Asklepian Amoeba70 gp or 1 essenceSlime Bomb50 gp merchants fontus.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:33:24 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Asklepian Amoeba</title>
    <link>https://realmlords.dev/System/Magic-Items/Alchemy-and-Potions/Oozes/Asklepian-Amoeba</link>
    <guid>https://realmlords.dev/System/Magic-Items/Alchemy-and-Potions/Oozes/Asklepian-Amoeba</guid>
    <description>Asklepian Amoeba, also known as Bandage Slimes, are neutered oozes which still retain a keen sense for blood but lack any digestive capabilities. As a result they make for aggressive bandages, seeking out wounds to prevent bleeding.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:33:24 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>IX - Ambush on Pirate Island</title>
    <link>https://realmlords.dev/Campaign/Game-Notes/IX---Ambush-on-Pirate-Island</link>
    <guid>https://realmlords.dev/Campaign/Game-Notes/IX---Ambush-on-Pirate-Island</guid>
    <description> Seek vengeance for Iris upon the Xanthian corsairs encamped in a nameless mystic isle. Brewing terrible poisons, working aquatic sorceries, and lead by crimson caped Admiral Myn the mercenaries of the City of Gold engage nefarious schemes; yet little do they know that this day the red moon witnesses the AMBUSH ON PIRATE ISLAND Notable Loot Arkanythera Mechanism Admiral Myn’s Crimson Cape 30 doses of Xanthicon Book on Summoning and Aquamancy Rapier +1 12 shortbows from the City of Gold .</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:33:24 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>index</title>
    <link>https://realmlords.dev/</link>
    <guid>https://realmlords.dev/</guid>
    <description>Welcome to the world of REALMLORDS.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:33:24 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Fontus the Oozemancer</title>
    <link>https://realmlords.dev/Characters/Wizards/Fontus-the-Oozemancer</link>
    <guid>https://realmlords.dev/Characters/Wizards/Fontus-the-Oozemancer</guid>
    <description> acid burned face constantly weeping pores large jovial man of middle age Edges Once apprentice to Sabtah All-Grasping Divorced from a wealthy merchant of Amilus called Iris Sells Slime Bomb Asklepian Amoeba.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:33:24 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>