<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>REALMLORDS</title>
      <link>https://realmlords.dev</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on REALMLORDS</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>Photonic Guandao</title>
    <link>https://realmlords.dev/Mechs/Clan/Equipment/Photonic-Guandao</link>
    <guid>https://realmlords.dev/Mechs/Clan/Equipment/Photonic-Guandao</guid>
    <description>Requires 2 modification points to install. 5 energy damage, double damage against impaired targets, accurate. Threat range 2.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 02:32:04 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Communication</title>
    <link>https://realmlords.dev/Setting/Information/Communication</link>
    <guid>https://realmlords.dev/Setting/Information/Communication</guid>
    <description>No known form of communication can travel faster than light, instead messages are carried by ships moving between systems. By default ships entering a new system download an updated version of relevant information when connecting to the local datasphere, and provide these updates as they travel to other systems.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 02:19:53 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Emerald Harrier</title>
    <link>https://realmlords.dev/Mechs/Emerald-Harrier</link>
    <guid>https://realmlords.dev/Mechs/Emerald-Harrier</guid>
    <description>A light combat mech produced by the Florian League. The J-Series are designed to be an affordable version which they sell to external parties. Size: 1/2 Armor: 0 Save Target: 10 Sensors: 9 E-Defense: 8 Tech Attack: +0 HP: 10 Evasion: 9 Heat Cap: 4 Speed: 5 Two Weapon Mounts (default two rotator canons) Rotator Canon: Range 10, 1d6 damage, become accurate if firing at same target for two turns Available Modifications Smoke Charge - Quick Action, size 2 soft cover for 1 turn Projected Shield - protocol, 2 penalty dice to and from a single target Smart Missiles - main weapon, 1d6 damage, smart Expanded Compartment - can carry an additional pilot or payload Deployable Cover - quick action, place 8 HP hard cover Bombard Canon - arcing, inaccurate, range 15, 1d6+1 damage.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 23:35:05 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Episode 9 - Bridge Over the River Gelland</title>
    <link>https://realmlords.dev/Campaign/Episode-9---Bridge-Over-the-River-Gelland</link>
    <guid>https://realmlords.dev/Campaign/Episode-9---Bridge-Over-the-River-Gelland</guid>
    <description> Will the people of Gelland be able to escape their beleaguered town before itchy-fingered forces of Galt demolish their only way of escape? James repairs a familiar model of appropriated mechs under the cover of Dr.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 20:47:33 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Episode 8 - Independent People&#039;s Republic of Galt</title>
    <link>https://realmlords.dev/Campaign/Episode-8---Independent-People's-Republic-of-Galt</link>
    <guid>https://realmlords.dev/Campaign/Episode-8---Independent-People's-Republic-of-Galt</guid>
    <description> Under the guise of a delivery mission the crew discover the people of idyllic Gelland are held hostage by their own government, meanwhile the Katangan’s puppets are the barbarians at the gates.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 07:15:18 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Episode 7 - Scrapyard Jump</title>
    <link>https://realmlords.dev/Campaign/Episode-7---Scrapyard-Jump</link>
    <guid>https://realmlords.dev/Campaign/Episode-7---Scrapyard-Jump</guid>
    <description> The crew return to Tartakover after their first successful mission, but nothing stops the mortgage. The crew learn of a number of leads: go on an uninsured ‘trade’ mission to the I’Sred*Ni, try to rob the Monarchy of Lod’s gigantic flagship, fight pirates in the Marrakesh subsector, or get in deep debt to find a Jump-3 drive to deliver aid to the people of Balleau.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 07:15:18 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Episode 6 - The Entity at Tyren</title>
    <link>https://realmlords.dev/Campaign/Episode-6---The-Entity-at-Tyren</link>
    <guid>https://realmlords.dev/Campaign/Episode-6---The-Entity-at-Tyren</guid>
    <description> The crew signs on the dotted line. The price of freedom is 3,000 credits per month. Plus fuel. And repairs. But the High and Dry is officially decommissioned by the Scout Service and in the hands of independent owners.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 07:15:18 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Episode 5 - Tartakover</title>
    <link>https://realmlords.dev/Campaign/Episode-5---Tartakover</link>
    <guid>https://realmlords.dev/Campaign/Episode-5---Tartakover</guid>
    <description> The crew watch a bank heist go wrong and contemplate how to get some credits. The Scout Service offers to sell the ship at a discounted rate, but the crew are still short for even a down payment on a 250,000 credit purchase.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 21:20:05 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Episode 4 - Volcano</title>
    <link>https://realmlords.dev/Campaign/Episode-4---Volcano</link>
    <guid>https://realmlords.dev/Campaign/Episode-4---Volcano</guid>
    <description>The travelers perform a heroic rescue and are thanked by the people of Chubbuck. Alongside the people the High and Dry saves two containers of quasi-legal antimatter stored in the volcano.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 20:53:44 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Episode 3 - Chubbuck Mountain</title>
    <link>https://realmlords.dev/Campaign/Episode-3---Chubbuck-Mountain</link>
    <guid>https://realmlords.dev/Campaign/Episode-3---Chubbuck-Mountain</guid>
    <description>Travelers fight locust, local scrappers, altitude sickness, and wild beasts to secure the High and Dry atop Mount Chubbuck.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 18:55:39 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>